(Penny:)Well, now I miss him even more.
(Sheldon:)Well, if it's any consolation,
I'm sure Leonard's tormented
(Sheldon:)every moment he's away from your
warm embrace and cherry lips.
(Raj:)-Thanks.
-Oh! Seriously?
(Raj:)-Excuse me, Mrs. Davis?
-What?
(Raj:)I'd like to apologize
for being insensitive.
(Raj:)And for possibly making penguins
seem like jerks,
because 99 percent of them
are stand-up guys.
(Mrs Davis:)Forget about it.
You know, you and I--
you and I have a lot in common.
(Mrs Davis:)-Is that right?
-Oh, yes. I--
(Raj:)I, too,
am in the throes of heartbreak.
(Raj:)Okay, fine,
I'll tell you about it.
(Sheldon:)Here is a hot beverage
to comfort you.
(Sheldon:)It's in a to-go cup.
Make of that what you will.